

Timothy Keaveny

Software Engineer

I'm a Software Engineer and Cybersecurity enthusiast who got his start in programming via a Raspberry Pi and a 2016 immersive pilot program for wounded veterans, hosted by Ft. Belvoir WTB and Amazon Web Services at their Herndon, VA HQ office.

In addition to this, I have also attended two immersive bootcamps, one for Full Stack Web Development at General Assembly (14 weeks at 8 hrs a day 5x weekly) and another for Penetration Testing at Hacker USA (6 months at 5 hrs a day 2x weekly).

I attended & completed both bootcamps simultaneously while working full-time at the New York Division of Military & Naval Affairs, 120 miles away. I only mention this to demonstrate my commitment and passion.

Organized, mission-focused, and detail-oriented is how I would describe myself, owing to 10 years of military service in financial management and network operations.

I have thorough experience with technologies such as Python, vanilla JavaScript, Node.js, React, Linux, Bash scripting, AWS cloud platform, Serverless architecture, and much more than I can fit within this description.

Address

35 Hampton street Albany, NY 12209

Phone

+1 (718) 249-9308

Email

timothy.keaveny@devopsec.io

LinkedIn

www.linkedin.com/in/timothykeaveny

Github

https://github.com/harlemtraveler

Web

https://devopsec.io Nationality

American

Education

2018

General Assembly

Web Development Immersive Coding Bootcamp

2016 - 2018

Udacity

Nanodegrees: Intro to Programming & Full Stack Web Development

Experience

2019 - current

Founder & Lead Engineer

DevOpSec LLC

Technology consultancy that specializes in serving American government & business entities operating in the Southeast Asian region. Services provided are focused on DevOps, Serverless architecture, and security.

2020 - current

Founder, Operations, and Sales Lead

Harlem Botanicals LLC

Direct import & online wholesale of SE Asian goods, specializing in products such as coffee. Manufacturing, material supply, lab space, etc is all managed in-house, with the exception of micro-bio testing.

2019

Junior Developer

Reflexions Data LLC

Frontend & backend development on PHP/MySQL applications, as well as Craft CMS

2018

Technologist Intern

Troy Web Consulting

Full Stack Web Development, working directly with clients for production Laravel/MySQL

2018

Engineering Fellow

General Assembly

Mentor students and alumni on Web Development

2013 - 2018

2017 - 2018

Financial Mgmt Tech

NY Division of Military & Naval Affairs

Manage pay & assets - NY ARNG

Network Operations Specialist, 42ID

Skills

Python, JavaScript

AWS

Kubernetes

React, Node.js

Penetration Testing

Linux

Computer Vision

Languages

English

Tha

Chinese (Mandarin)